{
    "id": "7fa13281b62142cd84692ad0093027b7",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I suggested .......................... home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "her to go",
                "that she should go"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a7266dac841e43e2bd4e77b3cb024b71"
        },
        {
            "question": "We don’t allow people .................................... in the kitchen.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to smoke",
                "smoking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88b339c11dd74400a6b5df2213edd56d"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t ask him to .................................... the meal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "pay",
                "pay for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c06d0c2777b42378033b172f2fa4bc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I hate the thought .................................. old.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "of getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "649a84ecde874bcf8a891f3ca1847a4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The cleaning is ................................. by midday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to finish",
                "to be finished"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d6f32beb39542a7b587ba69f3dcfa00"
        },
        {
            "question": "She lets her children .................................... up very late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "stay",
                "to stay"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8523d02204114848ac1c90c230175491"
        },
        {
            "question": "We arrive ............................... New York on Tuesday morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c244fe9778a3450fb8a2cb46abb01f3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "These sheets are .................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to wash",
                "to be washed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3fedf82b90ab42b99860b51efbff472e"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor suggested .................................... a long holiday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to take",
                "taking"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bc02d1a3ce514be9a98d8daac9f3ff67"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you finished .................................... the car?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to mend",
                "mending"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "63405aaea28f417b9fbdd1b12dbef5a6"
        }
    ]
}